Characters, actions, places, occupations, and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
When you hug other people,
the world doesn’t have to stop spinning.
What if I lose?
Will I still get my reward?
This isn’t a prize for the winner.
It’s a reward for being amazing.
Try giving the people around you a chance.
Let them be a part of your life too.
I’m quitting.
I don’t want to do judo anymore.
Why do you think I need someone?
If you know you’re amazing,
come and hug Cheewa.
Just like that, the sky's full of stars, huh?
Isn’t it pretty?
Yeah, it’s pretty.
Hugging me made you feel better, right?
What? Who hugged you?
You were the one who hugged me.
But you were the one
who stepped toward me.
Nonsense.
If we refer to the free hug at the canteen,
when you opened your arms to me,
I took two steps toward you.
Earlier, I was the one
who opened my arms to you
and you walked two steps toward me.
That means
you were the one
who walked over to hug me.
If you know you’re amazing,
come and hug Cheewa.
I’m right here.
Nah.
Go home and sleep, nerd.
I still want to look at the stars.
Then go do that in your room.
Did you know I’m free this Saturday?
And?
Do you want to go to the planetarium
with me?
Why should I go with you?
It’s really beautiful there.
If you don’t go, you’ll regret it.
Who's going to regret it,
P’Niran or Nong Parncheewa?
If P’Niran doesn’t go,
will Nong Parncheewa cry like a baby?
I won’t cry.
I’m just asking.
If you don’t want to go, it’s fine.
It’s just that watching the stars alone
is a little lonely.
Alright.
We can go.
I’d be bored at home anyway.
Did you know—
I’m not going anymore.
Hey, I’m just kidding.
P’Niran,
if you’re still sad,
we can keep watching the stars.
I’m not in a rush tonight.
Mm.
Or we can go stargazing in my room
if you want.
You’re wicked.
Ugh, it’s Saturday.
Why do I have to wake up so early?
Dad’s out of town for three days.
Go eat at Auntie Tang’s.
Give it your all at practice.
Have you been waiting long?
Not long.
What are you taking me to do today?
You’ll find out soon.
I can't get you to spill, huh?
No.
Where are you going?
Are you going on a date?
Do you know him?
Yeah.
Kaomao, did you run away from your mom
to get out of homework today?
Let’s go.
Come on.
Is that yummy?
Do you want to switch seats with me?
It’s fine. I’ll sit here.
Use my hat.
Thank you.
Want a fan?
You like listening to tapes and old music?
Yes.
Just like my dad.
We have a record player at home.
He loves playing records.
Can I come over
and listen with you sometime?
Yeah.
It’s closed for renovation.
I’m sorry I didn't check beforehand.
Now we can’t go stargazing.
It’s fine.
Let’s find something fun to do instead.
Or do you have any ideas?
It doesn’t have to be academic.
Let’s go somewhere else.
I bet it’s still going to be academic.
Did you not hear a word I said?
This is not that educational.
Consider it an eye-opening experience.
You might like it.
No way.
Should we go somewhere else?
We came all this way,
so we have to do some sightseeing.
Sightseeing?
You call this sightseeing?
Come on, Glasses.
I feel like I’m on a field trip.
If you really don’t like this,
we can go home.
Oh, your face fell.
Why do you look so sad?
Come on.
Fine. We can hang out here.
Let’s go to the next room.
You’re smiling like a kid.
Can I be your little kid, P’Niran?
Are you hungry?
Yeah, a little bit.
I didn’t have breakfast.
Then we can grab something to eat first.
That sounds good.
A little something to make up for
not getting to see the stars today.
What do you mean?
The fried egg.
That’s your star.
You can look at it on your plate for now.
So creative.
Oh, what’s with that face?
Is it not good?
It’s too spicy.
Okay, then just eat the egg.
Do you want to order something else?
I’ll eat that for you.
I can eat it.
Here, eat your star.
If you can’t eat the rest, it’s fine.
Thank you.
But…
Stop talking. Just eat.
What are you taking me to see?
It’s an illusion.
It’s an optical illusion that tricks your brain.
You really like this kind of stuff, huh?
Or do you want to skip a step
and be friends?
You can.
Who knew coffee and the universe
could be the same color?
Now you and I know.
From now on, whenever you drink a latte,
you’ll think of the color Cosmic Latte
and think of me.
You really like this kind of stuff, huh?
Yes.
It’s interesting.
There’s so much more in this world
humans haven’t discovered yet.
I want to find it.
I’m fascinated by these things.
(When people like something,)
(you can see it in their eyes, right?)
(Like Cheewa right now.)
(He looks so happy.)
(It’s nice to like something)
(and be able to enjoy it.)
And what about you?
Huh?
Me? Oh.
You mean what I’m fascinated by?
Yes.
Hmm…
It’s hard to say.
I’m feeling kind of lost right now.
What I thought I really liked,
I don’t think I like it that much anymore.
But when I think about quitting, I feel empty.
I can’t really explain it.
I just can’t seem to let it go.
It’s frustrating, isn’t it?
I feel like I’m so indecisive.
Hey, don’t stress.
I… am fine.
I can watch you enjoy what you like.
I’m totally fine.
I mean it.
Let’s check out the next one.
Come on.
What’s this one?
No.
I see it differently.
How?
Let me give you an easy explanation.
It’s like the theory of gravity.
Gravity again?
Gravity is the attractive force
that Earth exerts on all objects
Just like my interests.
When I’m interested in something,
I try to draw it toward me,
creating a gravitational pull.
But when I feel like it isn’t right for me
and I don’t enjoy doing it
or feel happy doing it,
I’ll slowly stop attracting it.
I’ll enter a state of zero gravity.
In the end,
time will make us
drift out of each other’s orbit.
Do you get it?
Ah.
Is that a science kid’s idea
of a simple explanation?
Sorry.
You might not understand.
Thank you, though.
There’s inert gas and plasma
circulating inside.
If we touch it, it’ll keep following us.
Do you want to try?
I’m good.
You can touch it. It won’t shock you.
You do it. I’m good. I’m grown up.
Hey.
No.
I’m just like inert gas and plasma.
.What are you talking about?
I keep following you.
You’re such a kid.
I have to touch you first,
and then you’ll follow me, right?
We're only a few years apart.
And?
I’m not that much more of a kid than you.
You want a judo athlete to throw you?
No.
What? It’s obvious.
Cheewa, Grade 11.
Niran, Grade 12.
Isn’t that right?
We’re a senior and a little kid.
Or do you want to skip a step
and be friends?
Hmm…
But honestly, I don’t care much about age.
We can be friends if you want.
These look like jellyfish.
Even after having coffee,
I’m still so sleepy.
Did you know coffee doesn't actually
stop you from feeling sleepy?
It just tricks your brain.
Yeah, yeah, I believe you.
Save your explanation for later.
Is this smell from fabric softener or perfume?
I put on a little perfume.
Well, look at you,
wearing perfume when you're still so young.
You stole your dad's, didn't you?
Yes.
Why?
You don’t like it?
It smells nice.
Are we going to be here for a while?
If so, can I take a nap?
You can. I’ll be quiet.
Can I listen too?
The cord's too tight.
Oh.
I got this for you.
I know you love reading,
so I figured it would suit you.
Thank you.
This is cute.
Just like me.
Do you feel better after your nap?
Yeah, but I wanted to sleep a little longer.
Someone woke me up.
You did.
Should we come back here together sometime?
Huh? What did you say?
I couldn’t hear you properly.
Were there stars in your dream earlier?
And did you like the songs I played?
I don’t think that’s what you said.
Fine.
I won’t push you.
If I say I don’t remember, will you get pouty?
Both the songs and the dream.
No, I won’t.
Okay, I don’t remember.
You can play the songs for me later.
Okay.
It's actually pretty nice being here.
I get to look back on things
when I talk to you.
Even though I can’t find a solution,
it helps clear my head
just venting to someone.
Did you know
the Astronomy Club stargazes on the science building rooftop during breaks?
There’s a meteor shower
around that time too.
If the sky is clear, we’ll probably see it.
Come join if you’re interested.
To make up for
missing the planetarium today.
That’s interesting.
I don’t think I have to be
at the athletes’ village that month.
I’ll probably be so damn free.
That’s actually nice.
I can just lie down
and look at the real stars instead.
But it probably won’t be as clear as
seeing them in the planetarium.
That’s fine.
Do you want to keep walking around?
Sure.
I don’t want to go home yet anyway.
Or do you want to go somewhere else?
I can take you anywhere.
Well,
if I want to go to Mars,
can you take me there?
I’m just kidding.
Just wait until I grow up.
I’ll build a spaceship.
If you want to go to Mars,
I’ll take you there.
Yeah, let’s go.
Hurry up and build that spaceship.
I’ll be waiting.
Yes, sir.
Let's compete at this.
Shoot the basketball into the hoop.
Okay.
Did that go in?
No.
Watch your head.
You’re going to hit your head.
This is called a bed of nails.
It has sharp metal spikes sticking up.
But it won’t hurt you.
Because it distributes your weight.
Mm.
Ready?
No.
It won’t hurt.
Hey, come on!
Gosh!
Why are you smiling?
I got these two.
It’s okay. You did well.
Keep practicing. Watch me.
Oh!
Can we take a break?
We’ve been lost for over an hour.
Do whatever you want.
What are you taking me to see?
Cheewa.
It’s an illusion.
It’s an optical illusion that tricks your brain.
This is too much.
I don’t think I can take it anymore.
What did you bring me here for?
If you can’t handle it,
try doing what I’m doing.
What?
Does that really help?
Can you smile too?
I can’t, Cheewa.
I’m laughing at you.
Oh my god!
What’s all over my face?
Whoa.
So cool.
Whoa!
Why are you tilting your head?
You’re scaring me!
Come on, P’Niran.
Damn it.
P’Niran, come on.
I’m going to scoot forward like a kid.
Alright, I’m totally fine now.
I don’t have a headache anymore.
Aren’t you tired, Cheewa?
No.
What’s that?
It’s called a kaleidoscope.
Ah.
Try standing on the other side.
You’re giving me orders now?
Now, try leaning down.
Go to the triangle.
Put your face in.
What’s next?
Just look.
I like this one.
So many faces.
It’s funny.
From now on,
if you see triangle mirrors like these,
you’ll only think of my face.
Mm.
Why are you smiling?
What are you even smiling about?
Can I get up now?
I can’t stay kneeling.
I’m curious.
Is it possible for two stars
to end up close together?
It’s possible.
But the chances are really low.
It's like having two swarms of bees
fly past each other in the middle of the ocean
and hoping they'll crash into each other
midair.
I shouldn’t have asked.
If you’re confused, try to imagine it
as two stars kissing each other.
Their surfaces will be pulled toward
each other by gravity
until they end up sharing
the same atmosphere.
Their heat can reach
40,000 degrees Celsius.
After that,
the two stars will merge into one.
So that means if we kiss right now,
we’ll merge into one?
Do you want to try it?
You can find out if the theory is true.
Stand still and lean in.
Hmm?
Here.
Okay.
You have to close your eyes too.
Mm.
Go ahead and flash it.
Done.
Wow.
We really did become one.
Let’s go.
After you graduate from high school,
what would you study?
I’m sorry.
I just wanted to protect you.
Protect me?
Can you stop already?
This is none of your business, nerd!
Stay away from him.
Hey, Thara, play properly.
Sorry.
What’s up, athletes?
Aren’t you two going to eat?
Lunch break is almost over.
Yeah.
No, I’d rather work out.
Then how about we keep score?
Come on, let us join.
Go for it.
Hey, Niran.
Did you really have to
stoop as low as your ranking?
All you can do is attack from behind?
What a loser.
What are you talking about?
Look.
So what?
You did this and still have the nerve
to make that smug face?
Why would I do anything to you?
I don’t even want to see your face.
Why the hell would I do that?
Why did you throw a rock at me?
You’ve lost it.
You jerk.
You saw I came to school alone
and threw a rock at me.
When I ran after you,
you ran off and disappeared.
Pathetic.
Hey.
That’s enough, Oy.
What the hell is your problem with Niran?
Wasn’t the fight last time enough?
Go tell the teachers
if you think someone bullied you.
I don’t think you should accuse people.
Why would Niran do that to you?
He could take you down by himself.
He wouldn’t have to run.
Well, ask your friend that!
Ask if he’s ever run away from me before.
Last time you helped that nerd,
you ran away like a scared dog, didn’t you?
Huh?
What?
Hey!
Can you stop already?
This is none of your business, nerd!
Didn’t you just mention me?
Stay away from him.
Get lost before I throw you to the ground.
It won’t be as soft as a boxing ring floor.
Teachers!
This loser is pointing at my friend!
Thank you.
What the f*ck is wrong with Oy?
I don’t get it.
Honestly, when would you even
find the time to bully him?
You study with your friends,
train with me,
and go home with Cheewa.
You don’t have time
to do something like that.
With a jerk like Oy,
once he believes you did it,
there’s no changing his mind.
I think you need to find an alibi.
I’m usually not alone.
But the point is,
why the hell do I have to deal with this shit?
I’ll tell Teacher Suchart that you didn’t do it
and that you didn’t mess with P’Oy’s group.
I’ll protect you.
Mr. Parncheewa,
as your friend
ever since an asteroid
passed through the solar system
and passed by Earth,
today is the coolest I’ve ever seen you,
for daring to stand up and protect someone.
Someone he cares about.
I saw Cheewa staring straight at P’Oy
without even blinking.
Cheewa’s heart must be like
the star Regulus,
standing firmly on the side of what’s right
and always staying by the Moon’s side.
What the hell are you talking about?
Who are you guys?
My name is Jomyut.
I’ve been best friends with Cheewa
since that asteroid.
I’m Newton.
I’m best friends with Jomyut,
who’s best friends with Cheewa.
Ugh.
Let’s just say.
you two are Cheewa’s friends.
That’s it.
Yes.
Now that you two brought that up,
I want to talk about it.
Cheewa,
you don’t have to shield me next time.
You can't even fight. Don’t try to act tough.
What if you end up with a bruised face
or fall and break your glasses?
I’m sorry.
I just wanted to protect you.
Protect me?
Did you know that over 70% of Earth
is covered with water?
Let’s find time to teach you judo.
Are they even talking about the same thing?
It’s a language
only the two of them understand.
Ugh, who even are you guys?
Is your life better with your new schedule?
It’s a bit better than before.
Is it a hassle being my training partner?
Everyone else has already gone home.
Nah, it’s fine.
Thara,
can I ask you something?
Do you still want to keep doing judo?
Lately, you seem like
you don’t really care about it anymore.
I don’t know.
Sometimes I know
I’m not as good as you or Most.
We’ve been doing this since we were kids.
I haven’t gotten anywhere.
If you quit judo, what would you study
after you graduate from high school?
Accounting or business, I guess.
I’ll just do what my family wants
and get it over with.
Alright, stop being emotional.
P’Niran’s guardian is here waiting.
Did you know that our body language
can show how much pain we’re in?
Are you seriously good at everything?
I just want you to stop hurting soon.
I’m just tired.
About what?
Well, I’m tired of what I’m doing right now.
I don’t know if I made the wrong decision.
I’ve been doing judo since I was a kid,
but I’m only starting to have doubts now.
I’m unlucky this year, too.
I couldn’t get into the Athletes’ Village.
Did you know my family has let me try
so many things since I was a kid?
Sports like basketball and football.
Drums.
Piano lessons.
And so much more.
You know what you sound like?
Like that ad that talks about
planting trees, diving, seeing coral reefs,
and stuff like that.
I don’t talk like that ad.
I’ve actually done all those things.
I just feel lucky that
my family lets me try so many things.
Mm.
You’re lucky. Good for you.
I want to be your good luck.
We might not get to see the simulated stars,
but we ended up seeing the real ones.
This is so freaking good.
Do you want to wait inside?
There are a lot of mosquitoes out here.
You promised me earlier.
What promise?
Cheewa,
I want to ask you something.
How do you feel about my friend?
Honestly,
it’s nice being a 12th-grader.
We have so many fewer classes.
We have fewer classes,
but we have so much more to read.
Is that really a good thing?
Hey, Niran.
Why is Parncheewa being so clingy with you?
Just say you’re flirting with each other.
Shut up, Hem.
Flirting, my ass.
Don’t say that to Cheewa.
You’ll make him feel awkward.
I won’t feel awkward.
People naturally have a gravitational pull
toward each other.
Just like each planet
orbiting around the Sun.
Without these forces,
Earth might drift out of its orbit.
There’s one more interesting theory.
Like how planets are formed—
Hold on.
One question.
What are you doing here?
We’re here to study.
You're the only one with your mouth
wide open and those doe eyes.
Huh?
Me?
I’m doe-eyed?
Yeah.
If you don’t believe us, ask Jomyut.
You look so focused
on what Cheewa’s saying.
That’s right.
You seem to be interested in my friend.
I mean, really interested in
what my friend’s saying.
He’s just been telling me this and that
since we went to the planetarium.
The planetarium?
You went to the planetarium with him?
How?
When?
Tell us your schedule.
Oh, it’s not the planetarium.
It was some kind of science event, right?
Something like that.
What was it?
But we just went there.
There’s nothing unusual about it.
Well, you didn’t tell us at all.
Do I have to tell you guys everything?
No.
I mean, we don’t usually meet up
on weekends anyway.
We’re not middle schoolers anymore.
We’re grownups
and we’re going to university soon.
Yeah.
By the way, Cheewa.
There’s something
I want to ask you.
How do you feel about my friend?
If you don’t answer,
I won’t let you sit with us anymore.
Hey.
Can you not be so extra?
Whatever creative feelings Parncheewa
has for P’Niran,
that’s up to him.
What? You kid.
Stop it, guys.
Don’t make him feel any more uncomfortable
than he already is.
Don't overthink it.
Sit with whoever you want.
And Hem,
you pressed him about it because
you’re upset I didn’t invite you, aren’t you?
I’ll invite you next time.
This time, I was just stressed out, so I…
spontaneously went there to relax.
Oh, I’m not upset.
Yeah, stop it.
Quiet.
Or I’ll throw you.
Let’s go.
Jomyut, go to the restroom.
I don’t need to go.
Just go.
Fine, I need to go.
Cheewa,
ignore what Hem said.
He just rambles. He talks a lot.
What about you?
Are you uncomfortable with me?
No.
How do you feel about what my friend said?
What do you mean?
The fact that I’m hitting on you.
You’re down bad, Glasses.
You promised me earlier.
What promise?
You said you’d teach me judo.
Oh.
Well, just let me know when.
Are you still scared the guys
from the Boxing Club will bully you?
Even if I’m not scared,
I still want to walk home with you every day.
Once you learn judo,
you won’t have to be scared anymore.
If they start messing with you,
just hit them and throw them down.
Oh, I want to return the shirt
I borrowed from you.
I’ll go grab it.
Or do you want to wait inside?
There are a lot of mosquitoes out here.
Oh, I have mosquito spray.
Just come in.
You like that?
No.
Here.
You can smell it.
I guarantee it doesn’t smell bad.
Sunlight reacts with the detergent,
creating a subtle, pleasant scent
known as the sun-dried smell.
I have a secret to tell.
I hung this out at night.
Just kidding.
Oh, your face fell.
Isn’t that cute?
I drew it when I was a kid.
It’s heartwarming.
But why is there a guitar too?
My dad told me that back in the day,
he played guitar to win my mom over.
Uh…
What are you going to do next?
Probably nothing.
I think I’ll just lie around.
You should go home.
Here’s your shirt.
Okay.
Thank you for letting me borrow it.
You’re welcome.
I’ll walk you out.
You’re not going to bed yet, right?
Why?
What’s up?
You don’t want to leave yet?
He actually came?
What’s that?
A spacescope or a kaleidoscope.
I don’t know.
Just tell me.
I don’t know the exact name.
That wasn’t a question.
I mean, it has two names.
(You’ll see the person you like in there.)
(From now on, if you see triangle mirrors
like these,)
(you’ll only think of my face.)
(I like this one.)
(So many faces.)
Can I ask for something before I leave?
Just say what you want and hurry home.
There are a lot of mosquitoes out here.
Can I get a good night kiss?
Huh?
Now, touch your cheek.
That’s my kiss.
And this is yours.
(Well, if we kiss right now,)
(we’ll merge into one.)
The thing is
I see Cheewa in my mind all the time.
I’m already hitting on you.
I’m hitting on you!
The Astronomy Club has an activity today?
I’m exploring with the other club members.
Do you guys want to go up?
Let’s go.
We’re all here anyway.
Is that the face of someone excited to see aliens?
I’m not talking about aliens.
I’m talking about being with you.